themat.com 2000-05-26

# Your Privacy @ The Mat

At The Mat, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use the features on The Mat. 

The Mat does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Also, The Mat may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

The Mat does link to third-party vendors in our Wrestling Mall that allow the purchase of such products as books, movies, clothing and more. We strive to only partner with trusted third-party vendors, but you will need to contact such third-party vendors for their privacy policy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make your experience at The Mat possible and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. 

Tell us what you think - The Mat welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to [privacy@themat.com](mailto:privacy@themat.com)

Comments & Questions -- [info@themat.com](mailto:info@themat.com)
